[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Neil Armstrong was the first man to walk on the moon on July 20th, 1969. Who was the astronaut that followed him?", "correct_answer": "Edwin Buzz Aldrin", "incorrect_answers": ["John Glenn", "Charles P. Pete Conrad, Jr.", "Edward Smith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the best selling Barbie doll ever.", "correct_answer": "Totally Hair Barbie", "incorrect_answers": ["Midge", "Philippine Barbie Doll", "Olympic Athlete Barbie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A person who is excessively afraid of getting married suffers from what phobia?", "correct_answer": "Gamophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Wedophobia", "Entomophobia", "Acrophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Mrs. Robinson in The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "Anne Bancroft", "incorrect_answers": ["Elizabeth Montgomery", "Barbara Eden", "Patty Duke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Spader, Holy Hunter, and Rosanna Arquette starred in a 1996 movie called Crash.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Good the Bad and the Ugly, Sentenza is also known as Angel Eyes.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what way does Harold fake his death in the 1971 romantic comedy movie Harold and Maude?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["He slits his throat.", "He drowns himself.", "He hangs himself."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Catoptrophobia is defined as fear of mirrors.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dr. Watson is the sidekick of Sherlock Holmes. Do you know his first name?", "correct_answer": "John", "incorrect_answers": ["Oscar", "George", "William"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which member of the European Union completely surrounds two countries that are outside of the club?", "correct_answer": "Italy", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria", "France", "Spain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the volcanically active region that is situated in a famous national US park and has a territory of 55 kilometers by 72 kilometers?", "correct_answer": "Yellowstone Caldera", "incorrect_answers": ["Yosemite Valley", "Mount Shasta", "Cold Bay Volcano"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Tower of London was built primarily to function as a fortress, a royal palace and a prison.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]